<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/profiles"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-02-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Hoon Park</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/hoon-park/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/hoon-park/</id>
    <published>2014-02-04T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-12T17:14:07-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is an example article. You probably want to delete it and write your own articles!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Alex Jones</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/alex-jones/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/alex-jones/</id>
    <published>2014-02-03T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-12T17:14:22-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h3 id="who-are-you-and-what-do-you-do"&gt;Who are you, and what do you do?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi, I’m Alex Jones, the GM for the Codes team, based out of Austin, Texas. I’ve been building sites, products and services for the Internet since ‘94, working for a wide range of startups and agencies. I’ve shifted from development to design, to user experience, to product management and now to my role running this line of business. When time (and my awesome toddler Wyatt) allows, I dip back into coding and design. I start fires: sometimes sparking a community like &lt;a href="http://refreshaustin.org/"&gt;Refresh Austin&lt;/a&gt; and other times touching flame to charcoal to transform a few racks of cold ribs into hot, smokey perfection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an information junkie and voracious reader. I’ve begun to learn Python, thanks to &lt;a href="http://www.codecademy.com/"&gt;Codecademy&lt;/a&gt; and am brushing up on my Spanish via &lt;a href="https://www.duolingo.com/"&gt;Duolingo&lt;/a&gt;. For this post, I am experimenting with &lt;a href="https://editorially.com"&gt;Editorially&lt;/a&gt;, a Web-based text editor for Markdown. I still don’t buy into the value of Markdown, but am going to give it another shot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never spell &lt;em&gt;rhythm&lt;/em&gt;  right the first time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what-hardware-do-you-use"&gt;What hardware do you use?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For work, I use a 13” Macbook Air. I love this line of computers - they are so light, but powerful enough to handle all of the apps I run. At home, I have a four year old, 27” iMac that continues to rock. The giant screen, plus the processing power means the machine gets out of my way when I’m working on a design or code. I use a wireless keyboard and the Magic Trackpad for both. Gestures on the trackpad have made my life much easier and efficient, especially after customizing them with the free &lt;a href="http://www.boastr.net/"&gt;BetterTouchTool&lt;/a&gt; utility. When at work, the laptop sits atop a &lt;a href="http://www.raindesigninc.com/mstand.html"&gt;Rain mStand&lt;/a&gt;. The &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B003UYT4FK/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;amp;creativeASIN=B003UYT4FK&amp;amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;amp;tag=alexjones-20"&gt;Brenthaven ProStyle Slim Pack&lt;/a&gt; is the best laptop bag that I’ve ever used. I bought it specifically because I wanted something small to ensure I travel light, and it’s served well in this role for the last two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a space gray &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone-5s/"&gt;iPhone 5S - 64GB&lt;/a&gt; with this &lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/transaction/161630905"&gt;Rosewood case&lt;/a&gt; I bought from &lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/shop/NUTBOX"&gt;Nutbox on Etsy&lt;/a&gt;. I love both. I wrap my third generation iPad in a &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B007PA1K84/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;amp;creativeASIN=B007PA1K84&amp;amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;amp;tag=alexjones-20"&gt;Ridge case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have two &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/appletv/"&gt;AppleTVs&lt;/a&gt;, which we use to stream our media collection (we’ve ripped all of our CDs and DVDs) as well as Netflix and a few of the other channels. I’ve set the screensaver to display images from a &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/icloud/icloud-photo-sharing.html"&gt;photo stream&lt;/a&gt;, so the TV acts as a giant digital photo frame. On a side note, one of the smartest things we’ve ever done was to mount our living room TV to the wall on this &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B000WXH1Z2/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;amp;creativeASIN=B000WXH1Z2&amp;amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;amp;tag=alexjones-20"&gt;articulating arm&lt;/a&gt;, which has opened up our relatively small living room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use a standing desk at work and home. I scored a great deal on a &lt;a href="http://www.geekdesk.com/"&gt;Geekdesk&lt;/a&gt;, which is a motorized multi-height desk. Having an anti-fatigue mat is very important to save your legs and back, so I bought a couple of &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B005GZRS22/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;amp;creativeASIN=B005GZRS22&amp;amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;amp;tag=alexjones-20"&gt;GelPro Designer Comfort Anti Fatigue mats&lt;/a&gt; so I have one at home and one at the office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite notebook is the &lt;a href="http://dotgrid.co/"&gt;Dot Grid Book&lt;/a&gt;. The dots provide structure without getting in the way and the heavy paper provides a great writing surface. I use a &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/BIC-Reaction-Mechanical-Pencils-0-7mm/dp/B002VLA2OU/ref=sr_1_1?s=office-products&amp;amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;amp;qid=1392151255&amp;amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;amp;keywords=BIC+Reaction+Mechanical+Pencil%2C+0.7+mm"&gt;BIC reaction mechanical pencil&lt;/a&gt; with  .7mm lead. Together, they are a perfect pair for sketching wireframes and designs. Quality is worth paying for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the barbecue front, I have a large &lt;a href="http://www.biggreenegg.com/"&gt;Big Green Egg&lt;/a&gt;, which is by far the best smoker/grill I’ve ever owned. It can maintain a nice low 225° overnight without me checking it and it can crank up to 700° to serve as a pizza oven. It sits in a  table made by &lt;a href="http://jsdesignsshop.com/"&gt;JS Designs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For cooking, I use lump coal which burns hotter and lasts longer than standard briquettes or wood. I use small chunks of wood to help flavor the meat, preferring hickory, pecan and cherry. To start the fire, I use &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B001AN7RGG/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;amp;creativeASIN=B001AN7RGG&amp;amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;amp;tag=alexjones-20"&gt;Weber Firestarter Cubes&lt;/a&gt;, which make it super easy, without adding horrible flavors or odors to the meat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven’t posted my recipe for ribs or pork butt, but I have written up my method for &lt;a href="http://www.silverspider.com/2008/smoked-chicken-recipe/"&gt;smoking a whole chicken&lt;/a&gt;. As a tasty pairing, I highly recommend you &lt;a href="http://www.silverspider.com/2010/smoked-lemons/"&gt;smoke some lemons&lt;/a&gt;  to use as the base for lemonade. Top it off with a touch of bourbon to add a great kick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="and-what-software"&gt;And what software?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll start with one of the most important, yet underrated bits of functionality: backup. Having Timemachine baked into OS X has been great, but I also want an offsite backup for my home machines. Enter  &lt;a href="http://www.backblaze.com/partner/af1118"&gt;Backblaze&lt;/a&gt;. It works silently in the background and maintains revisions of every file for the last 30 days. For $5 a month per machine, it’s an easy purchase that has paid off a couple of times in the last two years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At home, I’m running Mavericks, the latest version of OS X. On the work laptop, I’m running OS 10.8 until Symantec updates disk encryption to support the new OS. While I await the update, I continue to use &lt;a href="http://totalfinder.binaryage.com/"&gt;TotalFinder&lt;/a&gt; to provide the tabbed browsing added to Mavericks as well as a few other handy modifications. &lt;a href="http://www.noodlesoft.com/hazel.php"&gt;Hazel&lt;/a&gt; automatically organizes files for me, based on rules I set up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://hyperdock.bahoom.com/"&gt;Hyperdock&lt;/a&gt; provides a window preview when I hover over open apps in the dock, which I love. &lt;a href="http://cordlessdog.com/stay/"&gt;Stay&lt;/a&gt; automatically arranges my app windows to the right configuration each time I (dis)connect an external monitor and pairs well with &lt;a href="https://mizage.com/divvy/"&gt;Divvy&lt;/a&gt;, which makes it easy to size and place windows where I want them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://agilebits.com/"&gt;1Password&lt;/a&gt; for OS X &amp;amp; iOS makes it easy for me to use complex and unique passwords, without fear of losing or forgetting them. This is one of the most critical apps in my day-to-day life and I’ve managed to get nearly all of my family to adopt it. Really, it’s that good - spend the money on the apps and put them into your daily workflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/intl/en/chrome/browser/"&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt; remains my browser of choice for computers and mobile devices alike. I have quite a few extensions installed on the desktop app, including &lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/adblock/gighmmpiobklfepjocnamgkkbiglidom"&gt;AdBlock&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/awesome-screenshot-captur/alelhddbbhepgpmgidjdcjakblofbmce"&gt;Awesome Screenshot&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/edit-this-cookie/fngmhnnpilhplaeedifhccceomclgfbg"&gt;Edit This Cookie&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/hangouts/nckgahadagoaajjgafhacjanaoiihapd"&gt;Google Hangouts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/personal-blocklist-by-goo/nolijncfnkgaikbjbdaogikpmpbdcdef"&gt;Personal Blocklist by Google&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://pinboard.in"&gt;Pinboard&lt;/a&gt;. I love that Chrome syncs open tabs across devices, making it easy for me to reference a tab on my phone that was open on my iMac at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most docs and spreadsheets, I use Google Apps unless required otherwise (tracking changes in a legal doc for example). With the recent launch of the updated &lt;a href="http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2013/12/new-google-sheets-faster-more-powerful.html"&gt;Google Sheets&lt;/a&gt;, I hope to be able to migrate away from Excel, as I’ll finally be able to use formulas for conditional formatting and work offline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For work email, I run Outlook to keep up with my returnpath.com address and use &lt;a href="http://mailplaneapp.com/"&gt;Mailplane&lt;/a&gt; for my OtherInbox account. I cannot wait until we’re all on Gmail and I can centralize. At home, I flip between  &lt;a href="http://airmailapp.com/"&gt;AirMail&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.postbox-inc.com/"&gt;Postbox&lt;/a&gt; to handle a few different accounts, not all of which are Gmail based. AirMail stops syncing after a while and Postbox chews up system resources. So yeah, no clear winner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href="http://visual.ly/minimalistic-gmail-cheat-sheet"&gt;Gmail’s keyboard shorcuts&lt;/a&gt; as much as possible. They are well worth learning, especially &lt;em&gt;e&lt;/em&gt; for Archive and &lt;em&gt;m&lt;/em&gt; for Mute. Seriously, it’s worth the time to memorize ‘em.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://db.tt/V3QKhP1y"&gt;Dropbox&lt;/a&gt; is integral to keeping all types of files in sync across my devices and &lt;a href="http://evernote.com/"&gt;Evernote&lt;/a&gt; remains a solid workhorse for keeping my notes in sync and searchable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://calca.io/"&gt;Calca&lt;/a&gt;, “the text editor that loves math” is a true gem. It has become my scratchpad for all forms of calculations. It’s human-readable and much more flexible than a spreadsheet. Here’s a simple calculation I ran a little while back:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Q3 Total&lt;/strong&gt; = 2,259,195&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End Q3 Total&lt;/strong&gt; = 2,329,151&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q3  Addition&lt;/strong&gt; = End Q3 Total - Start Q3 Total &lt;strong&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 69,956&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The value after &lt;em&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/em&gt; is calculated by the app, changing on the fly, and I can use &lt;strong&gt;Q3 Addition&lt;/strong&gt; as a variable in a new calculation. Awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It now runs on Windows as well as OS X.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I get to code, I use &lt;a href="http://panic.com/coda/"&gt;Coda&lt;/a&gt;, though I want to try out &lt;a href="http://www.sublimetext.com/2"&gt;SublimeText&lt;/a&gt; soon (I plan to set it up the way my friend Dave &lt;a href="https://gist.github.com/davatron5000/7215566"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For design, I tend to fall back to &lt;a href="http://www.photoshop.com/"&gt;Photoshop&lt;/a&gt;, though I try to utilize &lt;a href="http://www.adobe.com/products/illustrator.html"&gt;Illustrator &lt;/a&gt; in order to push my own boundaries. I hate their new licensing model, so I don’t expect to upgrade from the CS 5 suite that I’m currently running. I look forward to trying &lt;a href="http://www.flyingmeat.com/acorn/"&gt;Acorn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.pixelmator.com/"&gt;Pixelmator&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.bohemiancoding.com/sketch/"&gt;Sketch&lt;/a&gt; to see which will replace the Adobe products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href="http://tapbots.com/"&gt;Tweetbot&lt;/a&gt; on OS X and iOS to post random thoughts to &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/baldman"&gt;Twitter (@BaldMan)&lt;/a&gt; and I save interesting images to &lt;a href="pinterest.com/alex"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt;, including inspiration for the new &lt;a href="http://www.pinterest.com/alex/the-next-office/"&gt;Austin office&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSS is a core part of how I consumer information, so I use &lt;a href="http://reederapp.com/ios/"&gt;Reeder&lt;/a&gt; for iOS, and &lt;a href="http://readkitapp.com/"&gt;Readkit&lt;/a&gt; on OS X (until Reeder finally launches on OS X).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I save long articles that look interesting to &lt;a href="http://getpocket.com/"&gt;Pocket&lt;/a&gt; to read when I have time. Not only is it a handy place to collect them, it provides a clean reading experience on my iPad and iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href="bufferapp.com"&gt;Buffer&lt;/a&gt; to schedule tweets, many of which I automate using &lt;a href="https://ifttt.com"&gt;If This Then That&lt;/a&gt; to pull content from my site, Pocket, Pinboard and Pinterest. A couple of these feeds required manipulation, which was easy to do with &lt;a href="http://pipes.yahoo.com/"&gt;Yahoo Pipes&lt;/a&gt;. Hopefully Yahoo won’t kill this service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I run my &lt;a href="http://www.silverspider.com"&gt;personal site&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="http://www.wordpress.org"&gt;WordPress&lt;/a&gt;, where I aggregate posts from the aforementioned social networks and occasionally write.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days, I read books using Kindle for iOS. After repeatedly comparing prices with books in the iTunes store, it was apparent that Amazon’s prices were regularly cheaper. I do hate the DRM that they apply though, as it makes it much too hard to share a book with my wife. We buy and rent movies from iTunes, as Amazon doesn’t have a clean way of accessing and streaming these movies on our Apple devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At every opportunity, I purchase from Amazon. Prime is one of the best deals I’ve ever signed up for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I have a few minutes to kill and am not in the mood to read, I like to play &lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/letterpress-word-game/id526619424?mt=8"&gt;Letterpress&lt;/a&gt; on my iPhone or iPad, though the recently discovered &lt;a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/threes!/id779157948?mt=8"&gt;Threes&lt;/a&gt; has become pretty addictive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="what-would-be-your-dream-setup"&gt;What would be your dream setup?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While a bit more RAM in my laptop and a 27” Thunderbolt display on the work desk would be nice, I’m pretty happy with my setup. If/when Apple releases a Macbook Air with a Retina display, I would love to have it.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Andy Smith</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/andy-smith/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/andy-smith/</id>
    <published>2014-02-02T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-12T17:14:31-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is an example article. You probably want to delete it and write your own articles!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Nick Casares</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/nick-casares/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/nick-casares/</id>
    <published>2014-02-01T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-12T17:14:41-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is an example article. You probably want to delete it and write your own articles!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
