<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/profiles"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Rosemary Walsh</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/rosemary-walsh/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/rosemary-walsh/</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T13:45:14-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="who-am-i"&gt;Who Am I?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Rosemary Walsh and I am on the Service Operations team in New York working to improve and streamline service efficiencies. Previously at Return Path I have been both an Account Manager and a Client Success Expert. Before coming to Return Path, I worked at two different ESPs – &lt;a href="http://www.whatcounts.com/"&gt;WhatCounts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.fishbowl.com/"&gt;Fishbowl&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-hardware-do-i-use"&gt;What Hardware Do I Use?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I use a Dell notebook that runs Windows for work. I have a &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/ipad-2/specs/"&gt;black, 16GB Wi-Fi iPad 2&lt;/a&gt; at home. My iPad is always in a &lt;a href="http://www.dodocase.com/products/dodocase-custom-cases"&gt;DODOcase I customized&lt;/a&gt; to be Hot Coral on the outside, Teal on the inside, with a Gray elastic. I also use a &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone-5s/"&gt;gold, 16GB iPhone 5s&lt;/a&gt;. I also use my &lt;a href="http://www.usa.canon.com/cusa/support/consumer/eos_slr_camera_systems/eos_digital_slr_cameras/eos_rebel_t1i_ef_s_18_55mm_is_kit"&gt;Canon EOS Rebel T1i&lt;/a&gt; (with both the standard &lt;a href="http://www.usa.canon.com/cusa/consumer/products/cameras/ef_lens_lineup/ef_s_17_55_f_2_8_is_usm"&gt;EF-S 17-55 f/2.8 IS USM&lt;/a&gt; lens and a &lt;a href="http://www.usa.canon.com/cusa/consumer/products/cameras/ef_lens_lineup/ef_75_300mm_f_4_5_6_iii_usm"&gt;EF 75-300mm f/4-5.6 III USM&lt;/a&gt; telephoto zoom lens) for taking digital photos, but have found myself using the iPhone camera more and more as the quality of the camera improves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-software-do-i-use"&gt;What Software Do I Use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As organization and documentation are key to success in my role, I spend a lot of time using Google products. I use &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/chrome/"&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt; for my web browser, which I especially enjoy because I can login on different computers and have access to the same bookmarks, passwords, etc. I also rely heavily on Google Drive for the docs and spreadsheets, as well as my Google Calendar. Google Hangouts is my preferred means of online communication. I like that it stores all of your chats so that you can go back and look through the history. I find that I do this a lot when I know that I talked to someone about something but can’t remember the exact details. I have Google Hangouts integrated with &lt;a href="https://www.trillian.im/"&gt;Trillian&lt;/a&gt; to be able to chat with all Return Path folks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For tracking projects and status updates, I follow along &lt;a href="https://trello.com/‎"&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt; but find it ineffective for my own day to day use. Instead, I find myself typing notes in &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Notepad_(software)"&gt;Notepad&lt;/a&gt; daily. I spend a lot of time in Salesforce, and especially enjoy the ability to stay connected with others through &lt;a href="https://www.salesforce.com/chatter/overview/‎"&gt;Chatter&lt;/a&gt;. During the day, I usually listen to &lt;a href="https://www.spotify.com/"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;, although I enjoying listening to &lt;a href="http://rainycafe.com/"&gt;Rainy Cafe&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.rainymood.com/"&gt;Rainy Mood&lt;/a&gt; to help focus (you may have seen me Chatter about that). I am a big fan of &lt;a href="http://inboxzero.com/"&gt;Inbox Zero&lt;/a&gt; at work, but I have over 900 emails in my personal Gmail account and have &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/settings/storage"&gt;purchased additional storage&lt;/a&gt; for the photos, documents, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to rely on &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; on the web, &lt;a href="https://about.twitter.com/products/list"&gt;my phone, and my tablet&lt;/a&gt; for my news updates and &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; for photo updates. I use &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Amazon-Services-LLC-Prime/dp/B00DBYBNEE"&gt;Amazon Prime&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Prime-Instant-Video/b?node=2676882011"&gt;streaming shows&lt;/a&gt; and the free shipping, of course! I recently got a &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/intl/en-US/chrome/devices/chromecast/"&gt;Chromecast&lt;/a&gt;, although have so far found it ineffective since it has a limited number of apps that it can stream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When running I use the &lt;a href="http://www.mapmyrun.com/"&gt;MapMyRun&lt;/a&gt; app for tracking my route, accompanied by Spotify or &lt;a href="http://www.pandora.com/"&gt;Pandora&lt;/a&gt; for the music. I also have the &lt;a href="http://www.moves-app.com/"&gt;Moves&lt;/a&gt; app constantly running on my phone in the background to track my movements (walking the dog, walks to the train, etc.) It’s amazing how much you move in a given day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am in the midst of planning my wedding, so I also spend a good amount of personal time on Google Drive to share documents with my fiancé or family and friends. I created a &lt;a href="https://support.google.com/drive/answer/87809"&gt;Google Form&lt;/a&gt; to collect addresses that then fed the data into a Google Sheet. This was a major time saver! I also use &lt;a href="https://www.pinterest.com/"&gt;Pinterest&lt;/a&gt; for inspiration, as well as recipes for home. I have used &lt;a href="http://picasa.google.com/"&gt;Picasa&lt;/a&gt; a lot recently for uploading and editing photos.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Nick Casares</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/nick-casares/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/nick-casares/</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T13:45:54-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="who-are-you-and-what-do-you-do"&gt;Who are you, and what do you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m Nickolaus Casares, UX Designer, and I work on a team of designers that help deliver B2B software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been involved with design of some form or another for close to 15 years and was a sound engineer in a previous life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-hardware-do-you-use"&gt;What hardware do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At work, I use a 13” MacBook Pro connected to a 23” Dell monitor. At home, I use a 13” &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/macbook-air/"&gt;MacBook Air&lt;/a&gt;. On the go, I use an &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone-5s/"&gt;iPhone 5s&lt;/a&gt;, an old &lt;a href="http://amzn.com/B004HFS6Z0"&gt;Kindle Keyboard&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href="http://www.moleskine.com/en/collections/model/product/plain-notebook-large"&gt;large, plain Moleskine notebook&lt;/a&gt;. The iPhone doubles as my camera because as they say, “the best camera is the one you have”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I try to keep my hardware simple and independent of extra gadgetry. I regularly take public transit to work so keeping my setup light and portable is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="and-what-software"&gt;And what software?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried a lot of software over the years, and lately I’ve been keeping it fairly simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For productivity, I use Gmail, Outlook (at work), Google Docs, &lt;a href="http://evernote.com/"&gt;Evernote &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://trello.com/"&gt;Trello&lt;/a&gt;. Whenever possible, I try to use cloud versions of software so I can make a seamless transition between computers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gmail, Outlook, Evernote and Trello are probably the most used tools and form the core of my communication, note taking and task management systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stive for &lt;a href="http://inboxzero.com/"&gt;Inbox Zero&lt;/a&gt; so and I’ve honed my ability to follow the &lt;a href="http://lifehacker.com/use-the-two-minute-rule-to-stop-procrastinating-and-get-1521792128"&gt;2 minute rule&lt;/a&gt;. I tend to delete more than I archive, but I keep temporary project folders for work in progress and items that need to be tracked for follow up. I also keep one massive archive folders (organized alphabetically) for projects and reference material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a huge fan of &lt;a href="http://www.davidco.com/about-gtd"&gt;Getting Things Done&lt;/a&gt;, and I’ve tried at least a dozen systems over the past five years. After much experimentation, I’ve settled on Evernote as the core of my personal productivity system and Trello as the back bone of work task management. I tend to gravitate toward simple systems and both Evernote and Trello deliver a simple, multi-device experience that’s easy to update and share. I keep a single Evernote note for my personal GTD tracking and use a Trello board for tracking work related projects. When I need to buckle down and focus I crank up the tunes and practice the &lt;a href="http://pomodorotechnique.com/"&gt;Pomodoro Technique&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spotify.com/us/"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; is my go to music app, but I spend a fair amount of time listening to &lt;a href="https://www.focusatwill.com/"&gt;focus@will&lt;/a&gt; (especially when I need to buckle down and get work done).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m fairly religious about a daily and weekly review which is less about tools and more about process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to consuming information, I’m a huge fan of &lt;a href="http://www.instapaper.com/"&gt;Instapaper&lt;/a&gt;. Throughout the week ,I’ll set articles for “read later” and usually set aside an hour or two on the weekends to read the content I bookmark throughout the week. This can definitely be a time suck, so it takes some discipline to use this technique wisely. About a year ago I started implementing the &lt;a href="https://medium.com/life-hacks/9cbd3899b87"&gt;impending doom engine technique&lt;/a&gt;, and so far it’s working well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also a big fan of &lt;a href="http://quibb.com/"&gt;Quibb &lt;/a&gt; for industry news and &lt;a href="http://cir.ca/"&gt;Circa&lt;/a&gt; (iOS) for news headlines. For design news, I use the awesome &lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/geisha-dribbble-layervaul/jhiocdmmaannaccoofjfmjpbfkogmnap"&gt;Geisha &lt;/a&gt; plugin for Chrome which delivers fresh screenshots from &lt;a href="http://dribbble.com/"&gt;Dribbble&lt;/a&gt; and design news headlines from &lt;a href="https://layervault.com/"&gt;LayerVault&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my design work, I use Adobe Creative Suite, &lt;a href="http://www.axure.com/"&gt;Axure&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://balsamiq.com/"&gt;Balsamiq&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://redpen.io/"&gt;Red Pen&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.invisionapp.com/"&gt;InVision&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://verifyapp.com/"&gt;Verify&lt;/a&gt;. I also throw in a healthy mix of sketching and white boarding via photo uploads to Evernote using &lt;a href="http://evernote.com/skitch/"&gt;Skitch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For coding, I use &lt;a href="http://www.sublimetext.com/"&gt;Sublime Text&lt;/a&gt; and store my projects on &lt;a href="https://github.com/"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;. I use &lt;a href="https://www.virtualbox.org/"&gt;VirtualBox &lt;/a&gt; when I need to fire up Windows for browser testing a la the Windows virtual machines available from &lt;a href="http://modern.ie/"&gt;modern.IE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Must have utilities include &lt;a href="http://www.alfredapp.com/"&gt;Alfred&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://dropbox.com/"&gt;Dropbox&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.iterm2.com/"&gt;iTerm 2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://theolabrothers.com/sip/"&gt;Sip&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://lastpass.com/"&gt;LastPass &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.xmarks.com/"&gt;Xmarks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="whats-your-dream-setup"&gt;What's your dream setup?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, I’m pretty close to my dream setup. Five years ago I had a different answer but with the shift toward cloud storage and apps I’m a happy camper. I suppose the only thing I would like is a better way to quickly move photos between my iPhone and Mac (that’s still a clunky process).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would love it if Spotify started offering ultra high-resolution streaming, but that’s a topic for a different day.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Matt Henkel</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/matt-henkel/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/matt-henkel/</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T14:01:37-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="who-are-you-and-what-do-you-do"&gt;Who are you, and what do you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Matt Henkel, and I'm a Software Engineer on the Anti-Phishing Solutions team. I started at RP in June 2007: I spent the first ten months working in Application Support before moving into a Software Engineering role on Campaign Preview—where I spent four crazy years. Prior to RP, I provided application support for StorageTek and PAR Tech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My passion is meaning in data: helping with retrieval, architecting useful storage systems, finding hidden connections, and the like. To achieve this, I've been known to use pretty much any language, but lately I find myself coding largely in &lt;a href="https://www.java.com/"&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.ruby-lang.org/"&gt;Ruby&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://www.perl.org/"&gt;Perl&lt;/a&gt; here at RP, and with personal projects largely in &lt;a href="http://www.scala-lang.org/"&gt;Scala&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://golang.org/"&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.dartlang.org/"&gt;Dart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Besides coding, I'm a foodie (eater and cook), &lt;a href="https://untappd.com/user/guildencrantz"&gt;enjoyer of beer&lt;/a&gt;, coffee snob, board game geek, and role playing nerd. My best friend is an eight-pound chihuahua (the dog they call &lt;a href="http://firefly.wikia.com/wiki/Jayne_Cobb"&gt;Jayne&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-hardware-do-you-use"&gt;What hardware do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm waiting for a replacement for my work laptop, but I currently have a &lt;a href="http://www.dell.com/us/business/p/latitude-e4310/pd"&gt;Latitude E4310&lt;/a&gt; upgraded to 8GB RAM with a dock and a pair of &lt;a href="http://amzn.com/B007TNCMMU"&gt;Dell 2009wt monitors&lt;/a&gt;. Being a laptop the keyboard is horrible so for the last four years I've been using a &lt;a href="http://www.logitech.com/en-us/product/wireless-keyboard-k350"&gt;Logitech K350 wireless keyboard&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.logitech.com/en-us/product/performance-mouse-mx"&gt;Logitech Wireless Performance Mouse MX&lt;/a&gt; (not that the mouse gets much use). A key piece of hardware for me in the office environment is a good pair of headphones: I'm currently using &lt;a href="http://en-us.sennheiser.com/monitoring-headphone-studio-professional-audio-hd-380-pro"&gt;Sennheiser HD 380 Pro&lt;/a&gt; headphones. The biggest win in my hardware at RP is my desk: an adjustable sit/stand desk that saves my back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't usually take my laptop out of the dock (unless I'm taking it home) as I also have an &lt;a href="http://www.asus.com/Tablets_Mobile/ASUS_Transformer_Pad_TF700T/"&gt;ASUS Transformer Pad TF700T&lt;/a&gt; which is an Android tablet with a removable keyboard, effectively letting me switch it between a tablet and a netbook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My phone is a &lt;a href="https://www.google.com/nexus/5/"&gt;black 32GB Nexus 5&lt;/a&gt;. It's a solid phone, but most importantly it has &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/devices/details/Nexus_Wireless_Charger?id=nexus_wireless_charger&amp;amp;amp;hl=en"&gt;Qi wireless charging&lt;/a&gt;. I currently have four Qi charging points between my house, car, and desk at RP. It's a bit shocking how removing the necessity to plug my phone in has improved my enjoyment of the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also have two &lt;a href="https://getpebble.com/"&gt;Pebble&lt;/a&gt; smart watches (one original in grey, and one &lt;a href="https://getpebble.com/steel"&gt;Pebble Steel&lt;/a&gt; in brushed stainless steel) and recently acquired &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/glass/start/"&gt;Google Glass&lt;/a&gt; (Charcoal Glass with Split Tangerine frame). The watch has been quite convenient for providing small pieces of information in a subtle manner, however I still haven't figured out how Glass will integrate into my daily life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="coffee"&gt;Coffee&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm a coffee nerd, and here's my setup:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id="work"&gt;Work&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beans&lt;/strong&gt;: I recently stopped giving away my Starbucks gift cards and started using them to &lt;a href="https://tonx.org/better"&gt;buy credit&lt;/a&gt; with the &lt;a href="https://tonx.org/"&gt;Tonx&lt;/a&gt; subscription coffee service.
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Normally it's a bit expensive, but by actually using the Starbucks cards the price is pretty good—and the coffee has been very good so far.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grind&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.orphanespresso.com/Orphan-Espresso-Hand-Built-Coffee-Grinders_c_392.html"&gt;Orphan Espresso Lido&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;This is by far the best portable manual grinder I've used. The nice large burr grinds quickly and easily while producing an extremely consistent grind.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;This isn't made any more, but it looks like &lt;a href="http://www.oehandgrinders.com/OE-LIDO-2-Manual-Coffee-Grinder—PRE-ORDER_p_14.html"&gt;the v2 is available&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brew&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="http://aerobie.com/products/aeropress.htm"&gt;aeropress&lt;/a&gt; + &lt;a href="http://www.kaffeologie.com/shop/s-filter-for-aeropress-coffee-makers"&gt;S Filter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consume&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www.nostarch.com/mug.htm"&gt;Mug of Vi&lt;/a&gt; because :x.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id="home"&gt;Home&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beans&lt;/strong&gt;: I generally source my beans from local roasters such as &lt;a href="https://www.pabloscoffee.com/"&gt;Pablo's&lt;/a&gt; or defiant bean roasters—which has now merged with &lt;a href="http://www.bonfirecoffee.com/"&gt;Bonfire Coffee&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Occasionally roast my own with greens from &lt;a href="http://www.sweetmarias.com/"&gt;Sweet Maria's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grind&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="http://amzn.com/B00030IEJG"&gt;KitchenAid Pro Line Burr Grinder&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;It appears that this is also a discontinued product (mine's nearly 8 years old now), but it's served me well for everything from french press to espresso.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brew&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gaggia.com/e/machines.manual.RI9301_11.overview.html"&gt;Gaggia Baby&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;This is an entry-level espresso machine, but it's pretty hackable so you can easily improve the shot quality by replacing over pressure valve, and the make better foam by swapping out the wand.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.kitchenaid.com/shop/countertop-appliances-1/countertop-appliances-2/coffee-products-3/-[KCM0402ER]-401685/KCM0402ER/"&gt;KitchenAid Personal Coffee Maker&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;Getting a good, large, cup of coffee in the morning can be hard, but this does a great job of brewing at a sane temperature—this producing a consistent cup on those days when I'm too rushed to make an espresso or a pour over.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consume&lt;/strong&gt;:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Six shots of espresso travel in my &lt;a href="http://www.kinto.co.jp/en/products/drinkware/re_cup/"&gt;220ml ReCup&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Until ReCup comes out with a 500ml version (or the &lt;a href="http://sprudge.com/first-look-new-glass-keep-cup.html"&gt;KeepCup Brew&lt;/a&gt; comes out), I'm using a &lt;a href="http://www.shopvesseldrinkware.com/collections/porcelain"&gt;12 oz porcelain travel mug from Vessel&lt;/a&gt; (it's got a barrel of monkeys on it—I point this out because monkeys).&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="software"&gt;Software&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All my machines (personal and currently work laptop) run &lt;a href="https://archlinux.org"&gt;Arch linux&lt;/a&gt;. The core of my linux experience is my shell, which is currently &lt;a href="http://www.zsh.org"&gt;ZSH&lt;/a&gt;. I do not, however, run plain ZSH: I run &lt;a href="https://github.com/robbyrussell/oh-my-zsh"&gt;oh-my-zsh&lt;/a&gt; in addition to having ZSH automatically start, or connect to, &lt;a href="http://tmux.sourceforge.net/"&gt;tmux&lt;/a&gt;. Of course plain tmux isn't the prettiest or easiest to manage so I rely on &lt;a href="https://github.com/Lokaltog/powerline"&gt;Powerline&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://github.com/treyhunner/tmuxstart"&gt;tmuxstart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="vim"&gt;vim&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As most of my time is spent editing text I spend most of my time in &lt;a href="http://www.vim.org/"&gt;vim&lt;/a&gt;. While vim is pretty excellent by itself it's better with plugins, so I have to call out at least a few plugins:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/gmarik/Vundle.vim"&gt;Vundle&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Manage your vim plugins easily. It also makes it easy to back them up and get them on other machines.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/myusuf3/numbers.vim"&gt;numbers&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Show the current line number, but provide relative numbers for the other lines&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/godlygeek/tabular"&gt;Tabular&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Help keep things lined up nicely&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/tpope/vim-fugitive"&gt;fugitive&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Manage git from within vim&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.vim.org/scripts/script.php?script_id=1861"&gt;errormarker&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Get IDE style error notifications when you save a file&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/tpope/vim-obsession"&gt;obsession&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Vim sessions are extremely useful, but a bit of a pain to manage manually. With obsession, it's now trivial to get the benefits of vim sessions—especially if you use the following function: &lt;code&gt;vim() { if [[ (( $# == 0 )) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; -f Session.vim ]] then /usr/bin/vim -S else /usr/bin/vim $@ fi }&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://vim.sourceforge.net/scripts/script.php?script_id=356"&gt;dbext&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Don't wait 30 minutes for SQLDeveloper to load up so you can do a few quick queries, and don't fight with the horrible formatting of sqlplus: dbext shells out to the standard client for the target DB and then displays results in a new pane. You can even select and execute queries right from within your code.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/kakkyz81/evervim"&gt;evervim&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I put freaking everything in Evernote, and this just makes that content easier to edit.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And since I do spend so much time in vim (or on the shell in vim mode, or somewhere else that's in vim mode), one of the things that I've done that's absolutely amazing is swapped my ESC and CAPS LOCK keys system-wide. I could keep on with vim, but that's a talk all its own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="gui"&gt;GUI&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far that's all been in a terminal, but sometimes it's helpful to have a GUI, and that's why I run &lt;a href="http://awesome.naquadah.org/"&gt;awesome&lt;/a&gt;. Awesome is a hybrid window manager that I largely use in it's tiling mode. I've found that even though I was good at working virtual with desktops before, having a tiling manager has reduced the time I spend hunting for a window to effectively zero.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that there's a GUI, it's easier to admit that there are times when vim isn't the best solution and IDEs make sense (like when writing Java). When that's the case I use &lt;a href="http://www.jetbrains.com/idea/"&gt;IntelliJ IDEA&lt;/a&gt; with the &lt;a href="http://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/164"&gt;IdeaVim plugin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="browser"&gt;Browser&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, if I'm not editing text I'm probably in a browser. In my case that browser is &lt;a href="https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/google-chrome-dev/"&gt;Chrome, Dev Channel&lt;/a&gt;. Much like with vim, it's the plugins that really help the browser be awesome, and a few of the important ones I use are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://vimium.github.io/"&gt;Vimium&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I can even navigate most of the web without a mouse now.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/the-great-suspender/klbibkeccnjlkjkiokjodocebajanakg"&gt;The Great Suspender&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Don't let Chrome eat all your resources just because you might want to look at one of those 600 tabs again someday.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://evernote.com/webclipper/"&gt;Evernote Web Clipper&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Seriously, I use Evernote for just about everything. By default, I have Web Clipper add the tag &lt;em&gt;tl;dr&lt;/em&gt;, so  one of my primary uses for the Clipper is to grab articles to read later. The other one is to grab recipes to make later.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/proxy-switchysharp/dpplabbmogkhghncfbfdeeokoefdjegm"&gt;Proxy SwitchySharp&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;I have SOCKS servers configured for each of our environments and then switching rules setup for those environments so that I can hit things like the web interface for the production AMQ boxes without doing a local forward and pointing the browser at localhost.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://getadblock.com/"&gt;AdBlock&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Because ads make things slow.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/javascript-blacklist/emcepjkdiiaenmoaghcfghjjppbkbhnf"&gt;JavaScript Blacklist&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Because some javascript is evil.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/kindling-for-campfire/abnakpmgckdkcpgbcejajjbllagggcif"&gt;Kindling for Campfire&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;When I have three rooms open side-by-side in different tiles, it's convenient to switch to minimal view.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromeipass/ompiailgknfdndiefoaoiligalphfdae"&gt;chromeIPass&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;KeePass is the greatest application ever, and this extension makes it behave much like LastPass or 1Password in the browser environment.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id="passwords-and-other-important-things"&gt;Passwords (and other important things)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As mentioned above, I use &lt;a href="http://keepass.info/"&gt;KeePass&lt;/a&gt;. All my passwords and important text strings go in KeePass. KeePass has a few benefits over other services (such as LastPass and 1Password):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It's not hosted: my passwords don't go out to anybody else. The security is the same as the security to my systems.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I can auto-type passwords into any window, not just web pages. I auto-type passwords into everything (including shells) based on window type and titles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id="sync"&gt;Sync&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the drawbacks of the "[i]t's not hosted" benefit is synchronization. Well, I'm a huge fan of &lt;a href="http://www.bittorrent.com/sync/"&gt;BitTorrent Sync&lt;/a&gt; which allows you to automatically sync your files between your machines (even &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.bittorrent.sync"&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt;) without going through a third-party system—it's like Dropbox without Dropbox being able to see your stuff. I have all my passwords synced between three computers, my phone, and my tablet (I use &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.android.keepass"&gt;KeePassDroid&lt;/a&gt; on the Android devices) without issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of sync, I also run &lt;a href="https://www.insynchq.com/"&gt;Insync&lt;/a&gt; to sync my Google Docs (both RP and personal) to my machines. I find this quite convenient because now I just store all my documents together and I don't have to worry about what's local and what's in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="email"&gt;Email&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For email, I'm currently using &lt;a href="http://www.mozilla.org/en-US/thunderbird/"&gt;Thunderbird&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="http://exquilla.zendesk.com/"&gt;ExQuilla for Microsoft Exchange&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.1st-setup.nl/wordpress/?page_id=133"&gt;Exchange EWS Provider&lt;/a&gt; so I can access my corporate email and calendar (&lt;em&gt;when will we move to Gmail?&lt;/em&gt;). Of course I need to have at least some vim bindings, so I also rely heavily on &lt;a href="http://www.vimperator.org/muttator"&gt;Muttator&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="git--ssh"&gt;Git &amp;amp; SSH&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stock apps that almost all of us use (like SSH and git) have some extremely useful features that it's well worth digging into the options of some of these tools we use so frequently:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://git.wiki.kernel.org/index.php/Aliases"&gt;git aliases&lt;/a&gt; are extremely powerful
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Graph the commits: &lt;code&gt;lga = log —graph —pretty=format:'%Cred%h%Creset -%C(yellow)%d%Creset %s %Cgreen(%cr) %C(bold blue)&amp;lt;%an&amp;gt;%Creset' —abbrev-commit —date=relative —branches —remotes —tags&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Push to gerrit and add reviewers automatically: &lt;code&gt;pra = push —receive-pack='git receive-pack —re greg.colburn@returnpath.net —re matthew.unwin@returnpath.net —re lee.gonzales@returnpath.net —re Les.Barstow@returnpath.net —re mike.naseef@returnpath.net' gerrit HEAD:refs/publish/master&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://nerderati.com/2011/03/simplify-your-life-with-an-ssh-config-file/"&gt;SSH config&lt;/a&gt; can be used to accomplish magic
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;You can use ProxyCommand and (if you have keys setup) automatically hop through gateway boxes with &lt;a href="http://linux.die.net/man/1/nc"&gt;nc&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Host *.tst
User mhenkel
ProxyCommand ssh -q stage.tst.returnpath.net nc %h.lan 22
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h3 id="mobile"&gt;Mobile&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Nexus 5 is stock 4.4.2 (rooted) running the &lt;a href="http://getaviate.com/"&gt;Vviate&lt;/a&gt; launcher and &lt;a href="https://www.coverscreen.com/"&gt;Cover&lt;/a&gt; lock screen. The more location aware my phone is, the happier I am, and these two pieces of software really help make sure that I can quickly access what I need (and because there are things I always want quick access to I also run &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.fb.looprtaskswitcher"&gt;loopr&lt;/a&gt;). In keeping with the location aware (and time aware) stuff, I've also programmed out a fair few actions (such as launching &lt;a href="https://www.waze.com/"&gt;Waze&lt;/a&gt; when I get in my car or silencing my phone and launching &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.onemightyroar.lantern"&gt;Lantern: A Campfire Client&lt;/a&gt; when I get to the office) using &lt;a href="http://tasker.dinglisch.net/"&gt;Tasker&lt;/a&gt;. Do I even need to mention &lt;a href="http://evernote.com/"&gt;Evernote&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm also a big fan of seamlessly collecting stats about my life and as such I use both &lt;a href="http://www.moves-app.com/"&gt;Moves&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.automatic.com/"&gt;Automatic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My tablet is running &lt;a href="http://www.cyanogenmod.org/"&gt;CyanogenMod&lt;/a&gt; 10.2.1 (Android 4.3.1): no fancy lock screen or replacement launcher here. Other than Chrome, my most used piece of software on the tablet is probably &lt;a href="https://sonelli.com/"&gt;JuiceSSH&lt;/a&gt;. That being said, I do read on this a fair bit (with &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.books"&gt;Google Play Books&lt;/a&gt;), and watch TV via &lt;a href="https://plex.tv/"&gt;Plex&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On my Pebble I'm running &lt;a href="http://pebblecanvas.blogspot.com/"&gt;Canvas&lt;/a&gt; in app mode with data about the time, weather, and my next calendar event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Glass so far the &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/+/learnmore/hangouts/"&gt;Hangouts&lt;/a&gt; app has been my most used (besides the camera), but I recently got &lt;a href="http://www.shopxglass.co/"&gt;shop [X]&lt;/a&gt; and have been in some discussions about presentation (PowerPoint, Google Presentations) controllers. Sadly, while I can send stuff from Glass to Evernote, I can't query Evernote from glass; I'm sure it's coming, but it's not there yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-would-be-your-dream-setup"&gt;What would be your dream setup?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don't know what I don't know, so it's hard to say. Other than not yet having a really good task management solution across my devices, I'm generally pretty happy with my software situation. I'd love to see Glass extended more so I can do more without my hands. Additionally, I'd also love to see a device like the &lt;a href="http://www.asus.com/in-search-of-incredible/us-en/asus-transformer-book-trio/"&gt;Asus Transformer Book Trio&lt;/a&gt; which runs Linux and Android; ometimes I want a laptop and sometimes I want a tablet, but I never want to carry both. Oh, and an &lt;a href="http://www.hermanmiller.com/products/seating/performance-work-chairs/aeron-chairs.html"&gt;Aeron&lt;/a&gt; chair: I'd love to have an Aeron chair at RP again.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Margaret Farmakis</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/margaret-farmakis/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/margaret-farmakis/</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T13:47:14-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="who-are-you-and-what-do-you-do"&gt;Who are you, and what do you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Margaret Farmakis and I’m the VP of Professional Services. I’ve worked at Return Path for seven years, and I manage a global team of expert consultants focused on solving our clients’ most challenging strategic problems as they relate to optimizing their email programs. I’ve worked from three Return Path offices, starting out in the New York office, helping to open the London office, and now working from our Sunnyvale office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-hardware-do-you-use"&gt;What hardware do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Standard issue RP hardware: laptop, phone&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a &lt;a href="http://www.cisco.com/c/en/us/solutions/telepresence/ttg.html"&gt;TANDBERG&lt;/a&gt; phone in my office in Sunnyvale (My team is spread out across multiple time zones in the US, Europe and Brazil, so this is a great way to stay connected, but the primary way I communicate is email, phone and IM.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;mobile phone: &lt;a href="http://www.motorola.com/us/DROID-4-by-Motorola/88569.html"&gt;Motorola DROID 4&lt;/a&gt; (I need a slide-out keyboard and I don't love iPhones)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;wireless internet card: &lt;a href="http://www.verizonwireless.com/b2c/device/mobile-hotspot"&gt;4G LTE Jetpack&lt;/a&gt; on the Verizon network (I can work while I commute on the train from San Francisco to Sunnyvale three times a week.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-software-do-you-use"&gt;What software do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MS Office (mostly Outlook, Word, Excel &amp;amp; PowerPoint – I basically dream in PowerPoint)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google Docs (great for some things, but a real pain when it comes to complex spreadsheets with multiple tabs)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google Hangouts&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.adobe.com/products/adobeconnect.html"&gt;Adobe Connect&lt;/a&gt; (This is my favorite way to have a large group video conference so far. I'm in the process of getting a license for my team as I think it's much better than ReadyTalk and Google Hangouts.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.techsmith.com/snagit.html"&gt;Snagit&lt;/a&gt; (I take a lot of screenshots)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;AIM/&lt;a href="https://www.trillian.im/"&gt;Trillian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;ReadyTalk Quick Launcher (helps with common RT issue)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Firefox (almost always)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IE (sometimes; I use IE for GPPS and Firefox for Gmail so I can stay logged on to both at the same time. Also, I have more favorites in IE so sometimes just default to that for certain websites.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wiki (a necessary evil)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Skype&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropbo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;iTunes (although I’m an Android fan)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id="other-random-stuff"&gt;Other random stuff&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of life, I don’t know how I ever survived without Google Maps on a smartphone. I have a terrible sense of direction and I travel a lot, so this is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also read a ton, but don’t currently have a Kindle because I still like the feeling of turning actual pages and adding completed books to my home library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m in the market for a tablet or very light-weight laptop for personal travel, especially since I’ll be taking my sabbatical this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll all about green tea (not coffee) and love my innovative loose leaf tea strainer/brewer (Teavana Perfect TeaMaker), plus their tea is delicious and the have an incredible selection. I happen to love a combination of  green and mint tea combination. This is a great for people who want the benefits of green tea but don't like the taste of it. For example, at work when I make tea, I use both a green tea bag and a mint tea bag in the same cup.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Christine Borgia</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/christine-borgia/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/christine-borgia/</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T13:47:25-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="work"&gt;Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My personal operating system is all about simplicity and efficiency. I want as few tools and steps as possible to get things done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use Outlook 2010 for work email. I have a simple system of classifying, flagging, and filing, that helps me remember things I need to do or to get back to someone when I’m waiting for them. I’ve added button to my &lt;a href="http://office.microsoft.com/en-us/outlook-help/customize-the-quick-access-toolbar-HA010362102.aspx"&gt;Quick Access Toolbar&lt;/a&gt; in Outlook so I can categorize and file messages into my &lt;strong&gt;To Do&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Waiting For&lt;/strong&gt; folders in a couple of clicks. I categorize messages with the name of the person involved if it’s on my team, plus I have categories for my main areas of focus (client teams support, ISP knowledge, mediation, Radar/data, M3AAWG). Prior to each 1:1, I go through all of the emails categorized with that person’s name, and that gives me a quick look at what I owe them or what they owe me. I have very few folders for filing mail. Instead of deleting mail, I archive it, so those messages still show up in conversation threads. I delete everything older than 90 days from my archive folder to keep Gerri happy, and I use &lt;a href="http://www.dell.com/learn/us/en/04/services/ems-email-management-services"&gt;EMS&lt;/a&gt; if I need to dig up an old thread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I take notes in a plain spiral bound notebook and flag actions in the margin with a big star. Sometimes I use &lt;a href="http://office.microsoft.com/en-us/onenote/"&gt;OneNote&lt;/a&gt; to take meeting notes, and the integration with Outlook is great. I can create tasks and reminders from within OneNote, and I can send emails from Outlook to OneNote if I want to file them forever. I do this for account information, instructions, things like that. Regardless of where I take my notes, I have to remember to look back at the actions and make sure I’m tracking them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I track my team’s yearly/quarterly goals in Excel. I’m always looking for a way to do this better, as long as it’s &lt;strong&gt;SIMPLE&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For productivity, I loosely follow &lt;a href="http://zenhabits.net/zen-to-done-ztd-the-ultimate-simple-productivity-system/"&gt;Leo Babauta’s Zen to Done&lt;/a&gt;, a simpler version of &lt;a href="http://www.davidco.com/about-gtd"&gt;GTD&lt;/a&gt;. I do a weekly review:
* check progress against my goals
* get updates from my team
* go back through meeting notes from the week and pull out any actions
* look at calendar for the next week and make sure I’m not double-booked, that I’m prepared for upcoming meetings, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href="https://filezilla-project.org/"&gt;FileZilla&lt;/a&gt; for FTP, &lt;a href="https://agilebits.com/onepassword"&gt;1Password&lt;/a&gt; to store passwords, and I set up &lt;a href="http://office.microsoft.com/en-us/outlook-help/subscribe-to-an-rss-feed-HA010355679.aspx"&gt;RSS in Outlook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For work, that’s pretty much it—streamlined and simple.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="personal"&gt;Personal&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep personal and work separated as much as possible in order to support my work/life balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="hardware"&gt;Hardware&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m an Apple devotee with a white &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/iphone-5s/"&gt;iPhone 5s&lt;/a&gt;, a white &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/ipad-mini/"&gt;iPad mini with Retina display (Wi-Fi)&lt;/a&gt;, and a &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/macbook-air/"&gt;MacBook Air (brand new, fully loaded)&lt;/a&gt;. The MacBook Air recently replaced my &lt;a href="http://support.apple.com/kb/sp13"&gt;2007 “vintage” MacBook Pro&lt;/a&gt;. The iPad is a bit superfluous but is handy as a portable device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://amzn.com/B00AWH595M"&gt;Kindle Paperwhite (2nd generation)&lt;/a&gt;—I have used a &lt;a href="http://amzn.com/B0015T963C"&gt;Kindle 2&lt;/a&gt; (2nd generation Kindle) for years, and I thought it couldn’t be improved upon. But when a family member recently dropped something heavy on it, I had to replace it. I would have bought another Kindle 2, but I was drawn to the background light on the Paperwhite, which is awesome and totally worth the upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="software"&gt;Software&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://evernote.com/"&gt;Evernote&lt;/a&gt; for filing away all sorts of information—it’s &lt;a href="http://appstore.com/evernote/evernote/"&gt;synced on my iPhone and iPad&lt;/a&gt;, so I can always have the information at my fingertips. I keep my favorite recipes on here, articles I want to save, medical history for my family plus all information I might need if someone got hurt, favorite workouts, reading lists, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://getpocket.com/"&gt;Pocket&lt;/a&gt; for marking something to read later—after I read it, if I like it and want to keep it, I then put it in Evernote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rememberthemilk.com/"&gt;Remember the Milk&lt;/a&gt; for task management—I have a list for routine tasks so I remember to do them – it’s the only way I remember to clean the air filter every three months, pay bills weekly, get my flu shot, etc. I also keep my shopping list on RTM so any time I’m out I remember what I need to pick up. I hooked RTM up to &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/ios/siri/"&gt;Siri&lt;/a&gt; so she tells RTM when I ask her to remind me of something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://digg.com/reader"&gt;Digg Reader&lt;/a&gt; for personal blog reading—I seem to be the only person who doesn’t like &lt;a href="http://feedly.com/"&gt;Feedly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Andrew Harrison</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/profiles/andrew-harrison/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/profiles/andrew-harrison/</id>
    <published>2014-02-13T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-02-13T13:47:31-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id="who-are-you-and-what-do-you-do"&gt;Who are you, and what do you do?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Software Engineer, futurist, technologist, outdoor enthusiast, husband and father of 2" is what my LinkedIn profile says, which is accurate, if not a bit terse. I knew from a young age that my interests were in computers. I was the kid in elementary school who would rush to finish his in-class homework before the bus came to sneak in a few minutes of time on the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_II"&gt;Apple II&lt;/a&gt;. My first language was &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BASIC"&gt;BASIC&lt;/a&gt;, which I started tinkering with in 5th grade. I spent my first $900 to buy a used &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Macintosh_Classic_II"&gt;Macintosh Classic II&lt;/a&gt; in 1992 from my high school math teacher, Mr. Brown, who also got me excited about mathematics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up in a small farm community in rural southwest Nebraska, I had no desire to get lost on a giant University campus, and so found what turned out to be a perfect college for me in &lt;a href="http://www.rose-hulman.edu/"&gt;Rose-Hulman&lt;/a&gt;, situated on the outskirts of 'lovely' Terre Haute, Indiana. After graduating with a dual-major in Computer Science and Mathematics, I took a job in Indianapolis at Software Artistry, the company I had already been introduced to through my Senior project and co- op work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the end of college I had become fluent in &lt;a href="https://www.java.com/"&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;, the language I've focused almost exclusively on for the past 14 years. The software industry in Indiana was quite run-of-the-mill as far as exciting work goes, and after struggling to find jobs anywhere outside of the insurance industry, I looked elsewhere, setting my sights on Colorado, where I found ColdSpark, a small company trying to make it big in email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After 4 exciting years at ColdSpark, I did what many others from that company did, and found my way down the street to Return Path, where I will be celebrating my 4-year anniversary next month. Having the opportunity to transfer domain-knowledge can be rare in the software space, and it was refreshing to be able to start a new job at RP with some experience already in the email space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've bounced around quite a bit at Return Path, working at times on versions of InboxMonitor, InboxPreview, RNBL, SenderScore, and the project that became Inbox Insight. After the OtherInbox acquisition, I was presented the opportunity to join their Engineering group, working on what has ultimately become the Data Pipeline team, picking up the &lt;a href="https://www.ruby-lang.org/"&gt;Ruby&lt;/a&gt; programming language along the way, to great joy. Ultimately, my family and I decided that we would take a plunge and choose a change of scenery, and we closed on our house in Austin last July.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-hardware-do-you-use"&gt;What hardware do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id="work"&gt;Work&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My dev box is a &lt;a href="http://www.dell.com/us/p/xps-13-9333/pd"&gt;Dell XPS 13&lt;/a&gt;, with a solid-state drive, running &lt;a href="http://www.linuxmint.com/"&gt;Linux Mint 15&lt;/a&gt;. I also have to pair that with a set of &lt;a href="http://www.skullcandy.com/shop/inkd"&gt;SkullCandy Ink'd&lt;/a&gt; headphones (I have black, red, and gray). Oddly, I find some days I can't concentrate if I don't have headphones on, even if no music is playing. Oh, and a good ergonomic wireless mouse, as close in shape as possible to the &lt;a href="http://amzn.com/B00005BAUL"&gt;IBM 19K2002&lt;/a&gt; (I've worn two of those out over the years).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="home"&gt;Home&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tend to favor &lt;a href="http://www.asus.com/"&gt;ASUS&lt;/a&gt; brand hardware, buying barebones machines and then assembling them when they arrive in the mail. Our latest family "desktop" purchase was an ASUS laptop, running, sadly, Windows. As for smartphones, I run Android.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My most recent purchase was a &lt;a href="http://www.raspberrypi.org/"&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/a&gt; which came in the mail last week. I have plans to have it running Google Calendar, attached to a screen mounted near the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the kids, we've purchased Bo &amp;amp; Yana from &lt;a href="https://www.play-i.com/"&gt;Play-i&lt;/a&gt;, but they've yet to be shipped. I'm really looking forward to teaching my 2- and 4-year-old how to program robots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other hardware of note:
* &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apple_IIe"&gt;Apple IIe&lt;/a&gt;
* Macintosh Classic II (yes, the same one)
* &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SPARCstation_5"&gt;SPARCstation 5&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sun_Fire"&gt;Sun Fire&lt;/a&gt; X4100
* &lt;a href="http://www.usa.canon.com/cusa/consumer/products/cameras/slr_cameras/eos_rebel_t3i_18_55mm_is_ii_lens_kit"&gt;Canon Rebel T3i&lt;/a&gt;
* &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/nexus/5/"&gt;Galaxy Nexus&lt;/a&gt; (currently the 4, but will be getting the 5 once my contract is up shortly)
* &lt;a href="http://www.skagen.com/store/Skagen/en_US/shop/mens/mens_watches.html"&gt;Skagen&lt;/a&gt; watch (Titanium 205LTXN)
* &lt;a href="http://www.adidas.com/us/product/mens-running-kanadia-trail-6-shoes/IET62"&gt;Adidas Kanadia TR&lt;/a&gt; running shoes (I wore out two model 3s, wearing a model 4 now, and have a model 5 in the closet.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id="what-software-do-you-use"&gt;What software do you use?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Primarily I'm in a Linux environment, preferably a flavor of &lt;a href="http://www.ubuntu.com/"&gt;Ubuntu&lt;/a&gt;. I exclusively use &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/chrome/‎"&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt; for browsing, and &lt;a href="http://www.jetbrains.com/idea/"&gt;IntelliJ IDEA&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.jetbrains.com/ruby/"&gt;RubyMine&lt;/a&gt; IDEs for software development. For really hairy diffs, and especially when comparing folder/file structure, I use &lt;a href="http://www.scootersoftware.com/moreinfo.php"&gt;Beyond Compare&lt;/a&gt;. And yes, I'm an &lt;a href="http://www.gnu.org/software/emacs/"&gt;Emacs&lt;/a&gt; guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Online, one notable app I've come to love is &lt;a href="https://getpocket.com/"&gt;Pocket&lt;/a&gt;. You should check it out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
